<Document>
  ## Justicar

  A psychal wind catches on your coat, 50 meters to the south you feel the rythmic pulsing of a chant being sent out in waves across the noosphere- Their mind is weak and psyche unscrambled, a fanatic with no understand of what they do.
  You reach out into the leylines and pull until you feel a snap. The little ones are safe once more.

  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingHandsGlovesJusticarPsychalWrappings"/>


  The Justicar is the Psionic Warden of the Epistemic Cult, they serve the station as the primary method of dealing with processing and in some cases, destroying psionic entities, mentally, or by physical means.
  This role is equipped to study and interact with the various psychic phenomena in our galaxy, you will be tasked with protecting the epistemics vault, processing any psionic or magical criminals into the Justicar's hold, and holding various rituals to carry out the work of The Oracle - our blessed emissary of S'ath-Nareth.

  ## Loadout and Abilities

  <GuideEntityEmbed Entity="ClothingHeadHatJusticarPsychalCoif"/>


  In your loadout is a small selection of items to aid you in your task:
  -Your chestrig, a heavily armored chestrig capable of protecting you from any metaphysical threat that attempts to enter your hold.
  -Your Psychal wrappings and bodysuit, a valuable uniform with special sigil inlays that scramble the wearers mind, protecting them from most psionic damage and allowing the user to project their will through enhanced unarmed combat.
  -Mindbreaker toxin: A substance devised by the Epistemic Cult to combat those maddened by the power of psionics, and in general, those who would use them for nefarious purposes. This substance damages receptors in the ingested person's brain that allow for psionic manipulation, in some cases, this will leave the person in a comatose state alongside removal of psionic abilities (check server maintainers to see if scary mindbreaking is enabled or not)
  Optional loadout options:
  -LSD pill canister: a canister of space drug pills, these can help develop psionic abilities in any latent individual.
  -Cryptobiolin pill canister: a canister of Crytobiolin, take a pill of these to insulate yourself from rogue psionics powers, or to prevent them from using their abilities. Does make you feel drunk and talk funny though.

  Furthermore, you will start trained in three abilities:
  - Whisper Truth - A word neither here nor there, something horrible, something beautiful. You dont quite remember, yet you seem to remember it all too well. Make them remember too. On use the ability drives the target mad, silencing them for a short time and temporarily disabling the use of psionics. ( this encourages the target to go catatonic or kill their character while under the effect )
  - Psionic Assault - You gaze through them, 3 times today they've summoned a flare in the bar, you see the connection to everything they are and everything they will be- you pull it until it cracks. On use the ability stuns and disables the target, alongside psionically insulating and forcing the target to vomit
  - Sunder Mind - Hate. You harbor so much Hate. Show them what you hold in your heart. Make Them Leave. On use this ability will sunder the targets mind, instantly killing them. ( this is only usable under very specific conditions )
  ## Misc. information

  Other things you can do while not defending the vault and sundering the minds of the unenlightened:
  -Securing lotophagoi oil in a chem master in either your or the Mystagogue’s office. The substance is incredibly effective at unlocking psionic potential and healing psionic damage and as such, is highly valuable for those seeking to misuse it.
  -Assist in research, you aren’t just the psychic police, you’re a researcher too.
  -Conduct complicated rituals and get mad when the intern wont drink goat blood
  -Discuss with the chaplain about how the oracle works.
  -Argue with people that epistemology is a real science field and not pseudoscience. Cry as no one outside epistemics believes you.
  -Lead, due to your abilities and items afforded to you, you are officially the second in command of epistemics, and you are the first choice to be a standing mystagogue if there is not one present, the original was removed of their position via: being irrecoverable, demotion or some other method. For this reason you should be willing to cooperate with other departments in a manner your boss would, primarily security.

  Other notes and general advice:
  -Not every psionic is THE ENEMY, you can easily have someone be an informant if they also happen to have a metapsionic pulse, alerting you of areas of high psionic traffic. Get connections!
  -You may hand out forbidden items to other psi-enforcer on code red or white, they may prove greatly useful!
  -As a psionic warden, remember to not leave your charge! Leaving the epistemics area or Justicar hold is a violation of sop!
  -Do not forget the 415th Europan Ospreys Special Psionics Unit - our hearts will always be at megastructure 3317G
  -You are security liaison to epistemics, you are a specialist who deals in metaphysical threats and emergencies, you are to help manage other psi-enforcers and keep them in touch with the main force.
</Document>
